<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on xin iDEA iNNATA</title>
    <link>https://xinii.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on xin iDEA iNNATA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://xinii.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Windows registry settings that can help you work more efficiently</title>
      <link>https://xinii.github.io/blog/configuration/several-windows-registry-configurations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xinii.github.io/blog/configuration/several-windows-registry-configurations/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Registry settings for Japanese keyboard layout  About keyboard scan code Example of keyboard scan code Perform keyboard scan code mapping in the registry   Change keyboard layout for IME  Change Chinese input method English layout to Japanese keyboard layout Change the keyboard layout of input methods in other languages   Registry settings when an unknown icon appears in &amp;ldquo;My Computer&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;PC&amp;rdquo; in Explorer Registry settings when unable to connect to the NAS on the local network  References  Registry settings for Japanese keyboard layout About keyboard scan code First, what is the keyboard scan code?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some works after Windows 10 clean installation</title>
      <link>https://xinii.github.io/blog/installation/some-installations-for-windows-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xinii.github.io/blog/installation/some-installations-for-windows-10/</guid>
      <description>Activation of your Windows 10 slmgr -ipk {your product key} slmgr -skms {kms server address of your company} slmgr -ato Installation of some useful tools  Msys2 AutoHotKey Ricty  Configuration of msys2 pacman -S git fish tmux emacs gcc python cd ~ git clone https://github.com/xinii/xinconfig .xinconfig cd .xinconfig ./setenv fish exec fish set_conf tmux set_el auto set_el cn change_emacs xin emacs ssh-keygen -A emacs /etc/ssh/sshd_config #Port **** #PasswordAuthentication no cat {path to your pub key} &amp;gt; ~/.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add apt repository for Fish and Emacs</title>
      <link>https://xinii.github.io/blog/environment/add-apt-repository-for-fish-and-emacs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xinii.github.io/blog/environment/add-apt-repository-for-fish-and-emacs/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Command to be use No this command? Do this first Process  Register repository Refresh repository Installation    Command to be use add-apt-repository No this command? Do this first apt install software-properties-common Process Register repository add-apt-repository ppa:kelleyk/emacs apt-add-repository ppa:fish-shell/release-3 Refresh repository apt update Installation apt install emacs26 apt install fish </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Several SSH configurations</title>
      <link>https://xinii.github.io/blog/environment/several-ssh-configurations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xinii.github.io/blog/environment/several-ssh-configurations/</guid>
      <description>SSH interruption phenomenon  When logging in to a remote server with ssh, Write failed: Broken pipe may be displayed and the connection may be broken. It is necessary to change the ssh setting on the client side or the server side, because ssh is automatically disconnected by a timeout if it is not operated for a while.  Remedy  Deal on the client side  Describe the following contents in /etc/ssh/ssh_config or ~/.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a blog via Jekyll and post to Github</title>
      <link>https://xinii.github.io/blog/cms/create-a-blog-by-jekyll-and-publish-to-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xinii.github.io/blog/cms/create-a-blog-by-jekyll-and-publish-to-github/</guid>
      <description>The logo of Jekyll1Table of Contents  Install Jekyll Publish blog to Github  Install Jekyll Jekyll is a static website generation framework written in Ruby language. The following is the official website introduction.
 Jekyll is a static site generator. You give it text written in your favorite markup language and it uses layouts to create a static website. You can tweak how you want the site URLs to look, what data gets displayed on the site, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>