<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>environment on xin iDEA iNNATA</title>
    <link>https://xinii.github.io/categories/environment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in environment on xin iDEA iNNATA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://xinii.github.io/categories/environment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Add apt repository for Fish and Emacs</title>
      <link>https://xinii.github.io/blog/environment/add-apt-repository-for-fish-and-emacs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xinii.github.io/blog/environment/add-apt-repository-for-fish-and-emacs/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Command to be use No this command? Do this first Process  Register repository Refresh repository Installation    Command to be use add-apt-repository No this command? Do this first apt install software-properties-common Process Register repository add-apt-repository ppa:kelleyk/emacs apt-add-repository ppa:fish-shell/release-3 Refresh repository apt update Installation apt install emacs26 apt install fish </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Several SSH configurations</title>
      <link>https://xinii.github.io/blog/environment/several-ssh-configurations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xinii.github.io/blog/environment/several-ssh-configurations/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  [SSH interruption phenomenon](#SSH interruption phenomenon)  Remedy One more thing   SSH daemon on android by termux  Installation Setting the key Start daemon in debug mode Start daemon Login on the PC side    SSH interruption phenomenon  When logging in to a remote server with ssh, Write failed: Broken pipe may be displayed and the connection may be broken. It is necessary to change the ssh setting on the client side or the server side, because ssh is automatically disconnected by a timeout if it is not operated for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install OpenCV on Jetson Nano?</title>
      <link>https://xinii.github.io/blog/environment/install-opencv-on-jetson-nano/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xinii.github.io/blog/environment/install-opencv-on-jetson-nano/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Generate swap file Generate installation script Run the script Test the installed OpenCV  Generate swap file To prevent errors due to insufficient memory during compilation, create a swap file firstly, and store it to somewhere you know. After OS restarting, the swap space will disappear, or you can manually delete this file after the completion of the following compilation and other work.
$ fallocate -l 4G swapfile $ chmod 600 swapfile $ mkswap swapfile $ sudo swapon swapfile $ swapon -s Generate installation script The original link of the script to install the OpenCV 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Gnutls and compile Emacs from source</title>
      <link>https://xinii.github.io/blog/environment/install-gnutls-and-compile-emacs-from-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xinii.github.io/blog/environment/install-gnutls-and-compile-emacs-from-source/</guid>
      <description>The logo of Emacs1Table of Contents  The lack of Gnutls in the environment Potential problems Install Gnutls Other possible problems  The lack of Gnutls in the environment If the current environment lacks Gnutls, the following configuration is required before compiling and installing the Emacs source code.
./configure --with-gnutls=no Or specify the installation directory at the same time, add the option to ignore other dependent libraries that are still missing, such as the following configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>我的shell迁移记录</title>
      <link>https://xinii.github.io/blog/environment/my-shell-migration-record/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xinii.github.io/blog/environment/my-shell-migration-record/</guid>
      <description>Picture: High contrast utilities terminal1从bash到zsh 虽然我使用zsh shell两周后就换到fish shell了（关于fish shell下面有专门介绍）， 但这并不否认zsh shell仍然是个很好的shell。 你可以通过下面的方式从任意的shell切换至zsh shell。
 安装zsh时通过下面的指令：  brew install zsh (MacOS) apt install zsh (Ubuntu / Linux Mint)  如果你想要知道现在系统裡已经安装好的shell，输入下面的指令：  cat /etc/shells  如何将zsh作为你默认的shell呢？，输入下面的指令：  chsh -s /usr/local/bin/zsh  关于配置文件的读取错误  shell脚本解释出错时可以查看一下当前所使用的sh路径， 比如有可能是sh指向了dash导致出错。 通过下面的语句查看。
ls -l `which sh`  脚本解释器在语法上的不同点  从传统的bash等shell换到zsh时会发现集合的第一个元素的索引是从1开始的， 如果希望从0开始，在配置文件中配置下面语句即可。
 Fix array index for zsh:  if [ &amp;#34;$ZSH_NAME&amp;#34; = &amp;#34;zsh&amp;#34; ];then setopt localoptions ksharrays fi 配置zsh shell 与bash shell的.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>